[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "When you see what's going on, not just in Libya now but also in the Middle East, do you quite believe it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "Well, you can.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya", "Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Saddam Hussein", "Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "What should an American be thinking right now about these characters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "I don't know that I would lump Mubarak with Saddam Hussein or Gadhafi.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Much different?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Yes, indeed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "When you see this, do you feel uncomfortable when you watch it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Iraq"]}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "-- Tunisia, Egypt, Libya, do you not wish you'd waited perhaps?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I think quite the contrary with Iraq.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tunisia", "Egypt", "Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq", "Afghanistan"]}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", ",", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Who knows what's going to happen in Egypt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "There is an argument, and I have heard this espoused by family members of mine, who've served with the British military in Iraq and Afghanistan.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", ":", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Are they getting it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Well, there -- sure, there's a free press.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "When you see Gadhafi going, when you see potentially the House of Sal being threatened, when you see this complete transformation in the Middle East, do you feel excited or do you feel very apprehensive about what might happen, for instance, to Israel in all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, I guess you feel both.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House of Sal"], "LOCATION": ["Middle East", "Israel"], "PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "And that would be a threat to the United States, wouldn't it, if that happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Oh, my goodness, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "So if you take that as a potential scenario, if you were now in the administration, and was still defense secretary, would you be considering now an invasion of Libya because that would be the way to stop potentially what happened in Iran happening in Libya?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "No, I wouldn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya", "Iran", "Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Why are the people of Libya being left to die?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Because there was broad, uniform, almost un-debatable agreement that there was a risk of stockpiles of weapons of mass destruction in the case of Iraq.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Well, isn't that slightly disingenuous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "No, it's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "In Iraq?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "So if that is the yardstick for why Iraq happened, would you have been very happy to have gone in regardless of the WMD issue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "Did you have any regrets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Of course you have regrets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Have there been times during that period when you've shed tears over American troops?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "EX", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Oh, my goodness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Where were you the moment you heard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "I was in my office, having breakfast next door with a group of congressmen when the plane hit the World Trade Center tower, the first one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "And was what your first thought when the second plane hit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "WP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Accident.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "And who did you -- who did your gut tell you may be responsible?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I didn't have a gut feeling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "And these were people that you've worked with, that you knew personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Well -- yes, indeed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Is it always going to be confused in a situation like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "I think when something happens like that, there's a period where you have to sort it out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Didn't you have to do that for the soul of your country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Well, let me respond.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "CD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Why are we going after the guy who didn't appear to have anything to do with 9/11?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "I have -- to go back just one second.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Would America have gone to war with Saddam without 9/11?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Would you like it to have done it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "It depends on all of those risk factors.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WP", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Wouldn't your answer be an unequivocal of course it was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "He's the one who makes decisions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "But that's a copout, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "No, it isn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "If you'd been president you would have taken that decision?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "I think that's probably right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Was it a mistake to label this a war on terror?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Did you argue again it at the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Why were you overruled?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Well, I wasn't overruled, there was a discussion, and people had different views --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "I know, but why did he overrule you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Well, I don't know - I had several problems with the phrase.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "It's really a counterterrorism operation, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "It's no longer a war, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "I think that the word war is imperfect because it leaves people with the impression of World War I, World War II, it begins, it ends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Is America safer today, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "You bet.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "ORGAN: Isn't it extraordinary that the world's greatest military force can't find a guy on a horse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "You think he still alive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "That's the same thing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "No, it's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "The decisions that you took collectively?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "They're tough decisions, you bet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Because they were so polarizing these decisions, that inevitably there's been an extended blame game ever since?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "I don't think there has been.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "But there has, hasn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "You don't think so?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Not too much, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Compared to other administrations?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "You're in public life a heck of a long time before Iraq came along, for example.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "You mean sorry about the loss of life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "No, sorry about the decision making that led to it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "If you submit your resignation and he doesn't accept it, can't you just resign anyway?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "You could.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Do you wish you had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "I think in retrospect at the time, I felt very reluctant to walk -- our country was in a war, to walk away from it when the president tells you he doesn't want you to, is a hard thing to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["Libya", "Zawiya"]}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", ",", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "My colleague, Anderson Cooper, Anderson, what have you got on your show tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Here tonight, the latest from Libya, Gadhafi's forces seem to be gaining the upper hand at least in the battle for the city of Zawiya, poorly armed opposition forces and civilians under fire in that surrounded city.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson Cooper", "Anderson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["State Department"]}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "And you did say you just stand up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "It's still in the State Department.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "You still do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Why do you act like that's odd?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "It's just weird.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Didn't it dawn on you to take a rest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Condoleezza Rice"]}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Why would one want to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "CD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "You get up earlier than Condoleezza Rice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "And you do a proper workout?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "No, it's not proper at 78.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "What's been the human toll on you, do you think, from all that time you had in office, particularly through the very difficult years of the early part of the century?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Goodness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "On 9/11, you didn't call your wife?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Of course, it's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Why didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "Well, I was busy, goodness gracious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "Would you describe her as long suffering?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 654, "question": "What was it like for you, trying to juggle the two things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "Well, of course -", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "IN", "CC", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Drug prioritized?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "Drug addiction is such a terrible, terribly difficult thing and it's heartbreaking to see a human being you love go down and down and down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Did you think you had lost him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "Yes, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "When you see what's happening with Charlie Sheen and you obviously -- Martin Sheen his father feels helpless about the situation, is there any advice you can give someone when a son just won't listen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Well, I guess the only thing you can say is hope.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen", "Martin Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "All the profits go to military charities, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "They do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "But was he right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "You've served under four presidents, who are your political heroes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "I had respect for most of the people that I've worked with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "People you thought were genuinely politically heroic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Each one was different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "If you were to summarize yourself, would you say you're a dove or a hawk?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "I'm neither.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "You can write it right now on a tombstone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "He served.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110308pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Just that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]